D C  漫 画
我就不该和那个疯子结盟
I should never have allied myself with a madman.
他们在哪儿
Where are they?
在萨拉热窝 先生
In Sarajevo, sir.
他劫持了那个孩子
And he has the boy.
哇 看起来好像很疼很疼呢
Wow, that looked like it really hurt.
喔 等等
Whoa, now, hang on.
这像是还要疼上百十倍呢
That looked like it hurt a lot more.
不如 实践出真知 怎么样 小鬼
So let's try and clear this up, okay, pumpkin?
哪样更疼
What hurts more?
A还是B
A or B?
正手
Forehand?
还是反手
Or backhand?
大点声 小羊排
A little louder, lamb chop.
我猜你的肺可能萎缩了
I think you may have a collapsed lung.
再善谈的人也会变哑巴
That always impedes the oratory.
你真是粗鲁
Now, that was rude.
第一只小鸟还懂点礼数
The first boy blunder had some manners.
我想我需要给你上一课
I suppose I'm going to have to teach you a lesson...
好让你能跟上他的脚步
...so you can better follow in his footsteps.
算啦 我接着用撬棒扁你好了
No, I'm just gonna keep beating you with this crowbar.
侦探到哪儿了
Where is the detective?
还在路上
He's on his way.
但是 先生 他没法及时赶到
But, sir, he won't make it there in time.
好啦 小鬼 没有不散的宴席
Okay, kiddo, I gotta go.
玩得真高兴 对吗
It's been fun though, right?
也许我比你更开心一点吧
Well, maybe a smidge more fun for me than you.
你一直保持沉默 我只好这么猜测了
I'm just guessing since you're being awful quiet.
总之 当个乖孩子
Anyway, be a good boy.
做完功课 九点上床
Finish your homework and be in bed by 9.
还有 嘿
And, hey...
请告诉大侠 我向他问好
...please tell the big man I said, "Hello."
不
No.
杰森
Jason.
蝙蝠侠
红  影  迷  踪
哥谭市
五 年 后
放你的屁
The hell you say.
不是你召开的会议
You didn't set this up?
那是谁召开的
Then whose party is this?
我还以为是你们这帮东区衰仔
I thought it was you east-side losers.
你们已经投靠了黑面具
You already rolled over for the Black Mask,
我猜你们是要说服我们加入
and I figured you were gonna ask us in.
投靠
Rolled over?
黑面具在一个月内干掉了 我的六个手下 六个
The Mask whacked six of my crew in a month. Six!
是我最得力的手下
Some of my best people.
是你叫我们来开会吗
So you set up this meet?
不是 我还以为是齐奇
No, I thought it was Chi Chi.
不是我
Wasn't my meet.
管他娘的 老子走了
Oh, the hell with this. I'm gone.
你们这群白痴想留下
You brain donors wanna hang around...
坐下 弗雷迪
Sit down, Freddie.
是我召开的会议
It's my meeting.
是他 蝙蝠侠
It's him. Batman?
我们什么事也没犯
We didn't do nothing.
我们都知道那是句谎话
Well, we all know that's a lie.
你他妈的是谁 嘣了他
Who the hell are you? Smoke him!
我叫你们坐下
I said, "Sit down."
你找死吗
You wanna die?
自杀的捷径多得是
There's easier ways to kill yourself.
对 比方说冲一个手持AK-47的人大吵大嚷
Yeah, like yelling at the guy who's hoiding the AK-47.
听我说 你们这伙贩毒的人渣
Listen to me, you drug-peddling scumbags.
从今天起 我掌管毒品生意
I will be running the drug trade from now on.
你们八个是哥谭生意最火的街头毒贩
You eight are the most prosperous street dealers in Gotham.
我就跟你们这伙白痴做笔交易
I'm offering you morons a deal.
你们照旧做你们的生意
You go about your business as usual,
但要给我四成抽头
but kick up 40 percent to me.
黑面具只让你们吃残渣剩羹 跟我交易分得的油水多得多
That's a much sweeter deal than the scraps Black Mask is leaving you.
作为回报 你们将受到完全的保护
In return, you will have total protection
既防黑面具 又防蝙蝠侠
from both Black Mask and Batman.
但你们必须远离儿童和校园
But you stay away from kids and school yards.
禁止卖给孩子们 明白吗
No dealing to children, got it?
谁卖 谁死
If you do, you're dead.
好吧 疯子 你很慷慨
Okay, crazy man, this is all very generous.
但我们凭什么要听你的
But why in the hell should we listen to you?
卧槽
Damn.
包里是你们每位副手的人头
Those are the heads of all of your lieutenants.
搞定他们用了我两个小时
That took me two hours.
想见识一下我一整晚能有多少成就吗
You wanna see what I can get done in a whole evening?
别理解错了
Make no mistake.
我不是在征求你们的意见
I'm not asking you to kick in with me.
是通知
I'm telling you.
四成上供 我能接受
Forty percent works for me.
快 快 快
Go, go, go!
雷蒙德和丹尼呢
Where's Raymond and Denny?
刚刚被他抓了
He got them. Just grabbed them up.
妈的 快开 带我们离开这儿
Screw it. Just go, get us out of here.
我估计甩掉他了
I think I lost him.
-你们觉得呢 -我估计也的
You think I lost him? I think you lost him.
我觉得好了
I think we're good.
不 你们一点儿也不好
No, you're anything but good.
你们替谁干活
Who are you working for?
不替谁
Nobody.
瞧 我们只是偷了辆卡车 然后
Look, we just boosted the truck and...
再对我撒谎
Lie to me again...
脑袋撞墙将是你们今晚所受的最轻微的的痛苦
...and crashing into a wall head-on will be the least painful activity of your evening.
不 我发誓
No, I swear to...
那是什么啊 你们的货
What is that? Your cargo.
它叫亚魔卓
It's called Amazo.
亚魔卓是个什么鬼
What the hell is an Amazo?
高科技 全自动机器人
A highly advanced, cybernetic android...
能吸收超能力者的力量为己所用
...equipped with the ability to absorb the power of super humans.
哪种超能力者
What kind of super humans?
巨头级的
Big ones.
开了挂的面包机打人可不轻呀
Packs quite the punch for a toaster on steroids, huh?
-需要帮忙吗 -不
-Need a hand? -No.
那好吧 我就待这儿看好戏
Okay, well, how about I just stick around and watch?
另一个家伙是谁 穿紧身衣的帅小伙
Who's that other one? The pretty boy in the leotard?
那是夜翼 蝙蝠侠的第一个跟班
That's Nightwing. He was the Bat's first sidekick.
第一个罗宾
The first Robin.
你应该不只这点本事吧 老大
I think you'll have to do better than that, boss.
没错
I did.
管用吗 会减慢他的速度
Will that do any good? It'll slow it down.
是吗
You think so?
到高处去
Get to higher ground.
你知道他会飞吗 闪避
Did you know he could fly? Move!
我不介意你给几条建议
I wouldn't be offended by a few suggestions.
他有人类的弱点
He has the same weak points as a human being.
明白了 这可能会有一点儿痛
Got it. This might sting a bit.
激光 他会发射激光
Lasers. He's got lasers.
我不认为在他眼睛上贴两块油灰就能损伤他
I don't think putty in his eyes is gonna hurt him.
但塑胶炸弹有效 高招
But plastique will. Nice.
这箱货物本来是运给黑面具的
This shipment was meant for the Black Mask.
我不信你们胆这么大
I doubt you're behind this.
你们替谁干活
Who do you work for?
我发誓 没人指使我们
I swear. we're not working for anybody.
我们自己单干
This was our gig, all our idea.
放下它 好
Let it go. Right.
我说 我说 住手吧 住手
I'll talk, I'll talk. Just stop. Just stop!
红头罩 我们替红头罩干活
The Red Hood. We're working for the Red Hood.
我们别无选择 他
We don't have any choice. He's got...
子弹是从楼顶射来的 有狙击手
The shots came from the rooftop. A sniper.
技术很好
A good one.
目标已锁定
数据上传至卫星
看见他了 对
See him? Yeah.
目标已锁定
数据上传至卫星
喂 等等
Hey, wait.
行啊 把我丢下来陪他们
Right. Leave me with them.
自动驾驶
ACE化工厂——Joker起源之地
不 求你了 别过来
God, please, no. Stay away!
这是陷害 等等
It's a setup. Wait.
我不是坏人 我发誓
I'm not a crook, I swear.
不
No!
很难忘的一个晚上 是吧
Hard to forget that night, huh?
可以说 老蝙蝠 你的第一次重大失败就发生在这里
In a way, Batman, this was the site of your first great failure.
可能还是你败得最惨的一次
Maybe your greatest,
但肯定不会是最后一次 对吧
but certainiy not your last, right?
啊 回忆啊
Ah, memories.
我来哥谭是为了送这份情报
This bit of intel is what brought me to town.
幸好我总是挑准时间
Good thing I've always had perfect timing.
看看吧
Take a look.
读取
播放
放大
一个线人给了我这段录像
I got this shot from a snitch.
放大
他说这家伙最近在搞大动作
He says that this guy's been making some serious moves.
红头罩
The Red Hood.
可能是 他和初代有几分相似
Might be. He bears a resemblance to the original.
红头罩
罪犯
身份
不明
已知罪行：
非法闯入
盗窃
盗窃车辆
抢劫银行
非法交易
多人共同谋划抢劫银行
洗钱
好几个罪犯用过这个名号
Severai criminals have utilized this persona.
其中这位的嫌疑最大 不是吗
One criminal have particular interests tho, huh?
但他被关起来了
But he's locked up.
这也不是他的作风
Not his m.o. either.
非法交易额上升
There's been an uptick in heavy trafficking,
但犯罪率却下降了
but crime is down.
确实如此
Indeed it is.
过去两天里 布鲁斯少爷睡了差不多三个小时
Master Bruce got almost three hours sleep in the last two days.
真正的工作假日
True busman's holiday.
但他确实被关起来了
But he is locked up.
插翅难飞
Like, a lot locked up.
也许我们该去探探监
Maybe we should go for a visit.
你就不能说一次“我们上车”吗
Could you just once say, "Let's get in the car"?
说句话就那么难吗
Is that so hard?
阿卡姆疯人院
体形不错 经常锻炼
You look good. Been working out?
你们可能需要晒晒太阳
You could probably use a little sun.
不过 我又有啥资格说这话呢
Then again, who am I to talk?
他自称“红头罩”
He's calling himself the Red Hood.
你对他了解多少
What do you know about it?
他的着装品位糟糕透顶
That he has horrible taste.
我穿上那身行头时 那叫一个优雅
When I wore that number, it was classy.
更像衣饰奢华的餐厅领班 而不是像个摩托车恋物癖
More flashy maitre d' than motorcycle fetish.
当今的后辈们哪
Oh, these kids today.
如果你跟这事有任何关系 我们会查出来的 你甭想
If you're behind this in any way, we will find out. You're not...
小鸟儿 你比原来无趣多了
Oh, Bird Boy, you're so much less fun now.
人长大了 换上大小伙的长裤了
All grown up and in your big-boy pants.
但还是比他的继任强得多 不是么
Still, better off than his replacement, right?
变成蛆虫的食物后就讲不出笑话了
Even tougher making with the yuks when you're worm food, huh?
你这次你会下杀手么
You gonna do it this time?
还是只让我再裹六个月的石膏绷带
Or you just gonna put me in another body cast for six months?
太令我失望了
So disappointing.
回到刚才的话题
But back to the matter at hand...
这个新的红头罩
...this new hoody.
你真以为我会搅出那么多乱子
You really think I would stir up so much trouble...
却不明确地让你知道是我干的
...and not make sure you knew it was me?
我知道你以前从没见过他 但你要镇定
I know you've never met him before, but be cool.
他可是黑面具
This here is the Black Mask.
二十年来头一个控制了整座城市的大老板
The first boss to gain control of the entire city in 20 years.
在哥谭 他想要什么 就得有什么
Whatever he wants in Gotham, he gets.
但他的外貌有点儿令人不适
But his appearance takes a bit to warm up to.
他干了什么 什么
He did what? What?
这下好了 他正在气头上
Oh, good, he's pissed.
我们要关注的是那个 下令偷走机器人的主谋
Our concern is the one who ordered the theft of the android.
他的名号是“红头罩”
He goes by the name of Red Hood.
我才不管他自称什么
I don't care what he's calling himself.
你们这群蠢货知不知道 我有多少主顾等着竞拍亚魔卓
Do you idiots know how many bidders I had on Amazo?
登记那些傀儡独裁者和精神病人的名单 有我手臂那么长
A list of puppet dictators and psychos as long as my arm.
几百万美元打水漂了
Millions shot right to hell!
那是谁的钱 您的钱
And whose money is that? Your money.
我的钱 我的
My money. Mine!
这笔生意本来可以左右棋局
This score was a game changer.
拍卖亚魔卓可以让我一步踏入高层次的国际生意圈
Amazo was going buy my way up into high-end international trafficking.
现在我不得不继续在这个鸟不拉屎的破地方窝着
Now I'm forced to keep rooting around in this local leg-breaking garbage.
还给我惹来了蝙蝠侠
And he gives me bat trouble,
还把这笨机器人的头给我炸没了
who blows the damn robot's head off!
本来我还可以拿它当废铁卖
I could have at least sold it for scrap,
但蝙蝠侠连残骸也收走了
but Batman kept it.
是的 蝙蝠侠喜欢搜集战利品
Yes, Batman likes to keep things.
听着 这个杂耍的 叫 红头套...
Look, this circus act, this Red Foot...
红头罩 管他呢
Red Hood. Whatever.
他死定了 把他处理掉
He's dead. Take care of him.
你 新来的
You, new guy.
先生 别紧张 小子
Sir. Don't be nervous, kid.
但如果你继续那样盯着我看
But if you keep staring at me like that,
我就把你的眼珠挖出来
I'm gonna cut your eyes out.
把今晚的货物清单念给我听
Give me the specs on tonight's shipment.
是 先生
Yes, sir.
十箱各种型号的SMG(冲锋枪)和PDW(个人自卫武器)
It's 10 cases of assorted SMGs and PDws...
以及五千发点四五口径的ACP子弹…这是您最爱用的
...along with 5000 .45 caliber ACP rounds, your personal favorite...
还有两箱RPG(火箭榴弹)
...and two cases of RPGs.
货款均已清付
It's all bought and paid for,
今晚只是交货 不涉及钱
so this is strictly a delivery, not a buy.
但考虑到近期的事件
But in view of recent events,
我自作主张加倍了保安力量
I've taken the liberty of doubling the security detail...
并变换了卸货地点
...and switching the drop spot.
计划听起来不错
That sounds like a plan.
他们发什么呆呢 真是的
What are they waiting around for? Seriously.
喂 按规矩我只能停靠六分钟
Hey, protocol says I'm only supposed to be on the ground for six minutes.
没关系 我不会停留那么久的
It's okay. I won't be staying that long.
我差点以为他不会现身了呢
And I almost thought he wouldn't show.
你知道我最怀念什么吗
You know what I missed most about running with you?
各种玩具
The toys.
保持警惕 我们还没赢
Stay sharp. We're not done.
想共舞一曲吗 那就来吧
You wanna dance? Let's dance.
缆绳能支持住 不能
Is that gonna hold? No.
那你想让我  我应不应该
So you want me to...? Should I...?
行吧 杂活就交给我吧
Okay, I'll just take care of this.
好啊 今晚适宜竞速
Okay then. Nice night for a run.
-他是个高手 -嗯 上演了一出热闹好戏
He's good. Yes, he's putting on quite a show.
摄录
高 实在是高
He's very good.
我们困住他了
We got him.
不得不服 我们什么没见过
That's impressive. Nothing we haven't seen before.
你说了算
If you say so.
我们跟丢他了吗
Think we lost him?
闪避
Move!
你的敏锐不减当年
You haven't lost your touch...
播放
他有几手绝活 对吧
He's got some moves, huh?
虽然我讨厌长篇大论
And as much I hate to belabor a point...
但您依旧经常这样做
And still that is often exactly what you do.
那叫健谈 是我的魅力之一
I'm chatty. It's part of my charm.
我是说 这小子有些本事
I'm saying that our boy here has some skills.
他受过训练 训练有素
He's been trained and trained well.
看那儿 就这里
Like right there. That.
播放
暂停
在绳索套牢他的脚腕之前 他就切断了它
He sliced that cable off his ankle before it went taut.
回放
播放
这不是随意就能做到的
You don't just do that.
暂停
必须是训练过 练习过
That has to be practiced. Learned.
-还有那把刀 -刀怎么了
And then there's the knife. What about it?
你知道有多少刀能切断我的绳索
You know many knives that can cut my lines?
-不算多 -对 不多
Not many. No. Not many.
嗯 显然我们有了一个好对手
Well, look, we obviously have got ourselves a player.
我们 哎哟
We-ow!
阿尔弗雷德 送他回家
Alfred, take him home.
布鲁斯 我还可以帮忙
Bruce, I can still help.
你已经帮过了
You already have.
谢谢
Thank you.
回去休息吧
Go rest up.
好吧
Okay.
但如果你需要我 你知道去哪儿找我
But you know where to find me if you need me.
他刚才真的谢我了
He did just thank me, right?
确实是的 先生 怪事
Indeed he did, sir. Weird.
读取
你的敏锐不减当年
You haven't lost your touch...
播放
回放
暂停
载入...
音频
你的敏锐不减当年
You haven't lost your touch...
播放
当年 布鲁
...your touch, Bru...
你的敏锐不减当年 布鲁斯
You haven't lost your touch, Bruce.
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
博
物
馆
喔嚯
Whoo-hoo!
你们在办派对吗
You guys having a party?
我想 我们弄丢了邀请函
I guess our invite got lost.
结束了 谜语人
It's over, Riddler.
猜猜我的谜语
Riddle me this:
什么东西是绿色和紫色  外面覆盖着红色和黄色
What's green and purple but covered in red and yellow?
谜底就是你…当我踩在你的可怜屁股上时
You. When I land on your sorry butt.
别动 否则
Don't move or I'll...
否则怎样 射我吗
You'll what? Shoot me?
每秒发射二十发子弹 你们的速度还是太慢
Twenty rounds a second and you were still too slow.
我可不慢 小流氓
I'm not slow, punk.
我也不慢 我拿下他
Me neither. I've got him.
罗宾
Robin!
我不得不打倒他
I had to take him down.
你打碎了他的锁骨
You shattered his collar bone.
他是个毒贩子
He's a drug-deallng pimp.
我不认为在打倒他前 得先给他塞个软垫子
I didn't think I had to prop up some pillows before I took him out.
我们需要他交代
We needed him. He would've talked.
但你把他打休克了
But you put him into shock.
抱歉
Sorry.
我犯傻了
That was dumb.
但他罪有应得
But he deserved it.
也许我上次把要求说得太含混了
Maybe my last request was too mired in subtlety.
我要那个人死
I want this man dead.
我说“死” 意思是“死得很彻底”
When I say "dead," I mean seriously dead.
揍得他爹妈不识
Beaten, broken.
然后把他的脑袋挂在我墙上
His-head-mounted-on-my-wall kind of dead!
明白
Understood.
我们会对以后每一笔业务加倍的小心谨慎
We'll be taking further precautions at every transaction...
狗屁
Screw that.
要叫他知道 这是一个血肉战场
Time he learns that this is a contact sport.
我们要采取攻势
We're going on offense.
搅黄他的生意 搅他个天翻地覆
Rough up his business. Something big. Something loud.
当他现身来对付我们时
When he shows up to shut us down,
给他办一个派对
have a party waiting for him.
我说的“派对”
And when I say "party",
实际上是指一大堆人等着要杀他
I actually mean a whole lot of people who are gonna kill him!
-我猜到了 -明白就好
I figured. Just being clear.
你们干什么 我们是受保护的
What are you doing? We're protected.
我们向红头罩交纳了保护费的
We pay up to the Red Hood.
是吗
Is that right?
有意思
Cute.
你们知不知道惹的是谁
Do you know who you're messing with?
知道 泰勒·布莱姆福德
Yeah, Tyler Bramford.
你是一家夜总会的老板 还是东区的大毒虫 对吗
You're a club owner and some big damned drug dealer in the East Quarter, right?
我垄断着东区的毒品买卖 你们两个蠢货
I am the East Quarter drug trade, you stupid bags of...
礼貌点 肥佬
Manners, fatty.
我不管你的后台是谁 你管好自己的嘴巴
I don't care who takes care of you. You watch your mouth.
那么说 你知道我的后台是谁
Then you know who's got my back.
你知道我的上级是谁
You know who I answer to.
当然 红头罩
Sure. The Red Hood.
而我们 替那个即将夺回一切的人干活
And we work for the man who's gonna take back what's his.
就牺牲掉你的大屁股
So at the expense of your very wide butt,
给你们老大传递一条讯息
we're sending your boss a message.
好啊
Okay.
什么讯息
What's the message?
其实很简单
A simple one, actually.
想猜猜内容是什么吗
Want to guess what it might be?
我有几个猜测
I have a few ideas.
你们这些雇佣兵 有没有人知道我是谁
Any of you hired guns even know who I am?
你是我们的目标
You are our target.
噢
Ow.
你们四个装备有如此强大的火力 却甘于为金钱杀戮
So you four have all this power and all you do with it is kill for money?
据我的耳闻 你与我们同路
From what I hear, we've got that in common.
谣言不可信
You heard wrong.
我还以为你很能打
I thought you'd put up more of a fight.
打斗还没正式开始呢
Oh, the fight hasn't started yet.
我只是在拖延时间
I'm just stalling.
你怎么这么晚才来
What the hell took you so long?
闭嘴 战斗
Shut up and fight.
我得承认
I gotta say.
真怀念你战斗的身姿啊
I missed watching you work.
小心
Look out!
凑到鼻子跟前了
Awful close.
你担心自己准头太差
You afraid you'll miss?
黑面具要的只是尸体
Black Mask just wants a body.
我们不需要你的人头
We don't need your head.
放开他 靠边站
Let him go. And step away.
电击枪
A Taser?
要电就只能把我们两个一起电
Nail me and you'll electrocute both of us.
也许他正是那么打算的
Maybe that's what he has in mind.
不
No!
你该高兴我只杀了他们之一
Just be happy I only killed one of them.
他们都是杀手
They're all assassins.
那你又是什么
And what are you?
我在清洗哥谭市
I'm cleaning up Gotham.
比你的做法更有成效
More than you ever did.
你抢占黑面具的领地 杀掉所有挡你路的人
You're stealing territory from Black Mask and killing anyone who gets in your way.
黑面具只是计划中的一步
Black Mask is just a part of the plan.
计划 你变成黑帮头子了
Plan? You're becoming a crime lord.
没错 你制止不了犯罪
Yes. You can't stop crime.
这一点你从来都不明白
That's what you never understood.
我控制犯罪
I'm controlling it.
你想通过恐惧来治理他们
You wanna rule them by fear.
但你能把那些不怕你的人怎么样
But what do you do with the ones who aren't afraid?
我做的是你不愿意做的 我把他们都干掉
I'm doing what you won't, I'm taking them out.
告诉我你这是怎么了
Tell me what happened to you.
让我帮助你
Let me help.
已经太迟了
It's too late.
你曾经有过机会
You had your chance.
我的事业才刚刚开头
And I'm just getting started.
分析中
红 头 罩
杰森-托德
分析中
分 析  完 成
匹配
狗娘养…
Son of a...
你是说那混蛋又偷走了我的军火
Are you telling me that scumbag stole my guns again?
不 先生 他销毁了它们
No, sir. He destroyed them.
连卡车和司机一并炸成碎片
Blew up the truck, the drivers...
可恶 损失 太可恶了
Damn it. Of all the-Damn it!
之前 他只是把我们的人挖角过去
Previousiy, he was just enlisting anyone under our province to come work for him.
现在 他似乎干脆就把他们杀了
Now he just seems to be killing them.
那么说 又多了一个蝙蝠侠
Oh, so now we've got another Batman?
不介意血腥杀戮的蝙蝠侠
One who doesn't mind the blood?
不 先生 他不是蝙蝠侠
No, sir, he's no Batman.
他仍然从非法生意中获取巨额提成
He's still taking huge cuts from off the streets.
但现在 他要铲除竞争者
But now he's eliminating the competition.
他冲着您来了
He's coming after you.
谁能告诉我为什么那家伙还没死
You wanna tell me why this guy ain't dead?
我们尽力而为了
We're trying.
我们派出了恐怖四杀手
We sent the Fearsome Hand of Four.
四 我猜他们需要改名字了
Four? Guess they're gonna need a new name.
他妈的蝙蝠侠怎么还没把这渣滓从地球上清除掉
Why hasn't Batman wiped this little smear off the face of the planet?
也许他不想
Maybe he doesn't want to.
也许他想等你和红头罩斗个两败俱伤
Perhaps he's letting you and the Red Hood war it out.
他可能在等着 渔翁得利
He could be waiting-To take on the winner?
你以为这算什么事 网球锦标赛
What do you think this is? A tennis tournament?
我只是说 你是个蠢货
I'm just saying... You're an idiot.
你不了解蝙蝠侠
And you don't know Batman.
他不会放任这个疯子四处撒野
He's not letting this lunatic just run wild.
他是抓不到他
He can't catch him either.
或者还有别的原因
Or it's something else.
你感觉不到吗
Can't you feel it?
我们身陷他妈的交火地带了
We're stuck in the damn crossfire.
见鬼
Oh, hell.
先生
Sir?
喔 他想跑的话还跑得真够快
Wow, he sure can move when he really wants to.
您还好吗 先生
You okay, sir?
我没死
I'm not dead.
所以还行吧
So that's something.
好吧
Okay.
是时候改变战争态势了
Time to change up the ground war.
怎么办 先生
How so, sir?
我不得不与一个疯子谈判
I'm being forced into negotiating with a psychotic.
听起来不像好主意
That doesn't sound good.
不
No.
那将会是场噩梦
it's going to be a nightmare.
嘿 伙计们 还有十分钟就该查房了吧
Hey, fellas, 10 minutes to bed check, right?
泰瑞 你来这儿干什么
Terry? What the hell are you doing here?
你想我了么
You miss me?
我来顶罗斯曼的班
I'm covering Rothman's shift.
他得了流感 支气管炎 还是什么
He's got the flu, bronchitis or something.
这里交给我们 你何不去喝些咖啡
We got this. Why don't you grab some joe?
稍后我们去南翼找你
We'll meet you in the south wing.
这可不符合规章
That's not protocol.
行了 我无聊透了 我需要活动一下腿脚
Come on, I'm bored, I need to stretch my legs.
我们去 啊
Let's get...
抱歉 时间不容耽搁
Sorry, schedule to keep.
你们没必要杀他
You didn't have to kill him.
第一  我已经杀了他
One, yes, I did.
第二  我们给了你很多钱
Two, we're paying you a ton.
所以 第三 少说废话 赶紧把那扇破门打开
So, three, shut your gob and open the damn door.
输 入 密 码
他知道是怎么回事吗
Does he know what's going on?
他知道他能出去
He knows he's leaving.
只是在外暂住一宿 对吧
It's gonna be a sleepover, right?
我收拾好了我的牙刷
I packed my toothbrush.
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
韦 恩
托马斯
玛 莎
助手兼好友
杰森·托德
您需要照明吗 先生
Do you need more light, sir?
不 我看得清
No. I can see fine.
哦 您可以放心了
Well, there you have it.
他确实安息了
He's still at rest.
不 这不是他
No, he isn't.
这不是真人
That's not flesh.
布鲁斯少爷 您不能责怪自己
Master Bruce, you can't blame yourself...
我愚蠢又粗心
It was stupid and careless.
假人是高档橡胶制品
Body was made of high-end latex.
我把他带回家时却没有好好看看
If I'd bothered to look inside when I brought him home...
先生 您该记得当时您是多么悲痛
Sir, please, remember how distraught you were.
连我也感觉
Even I found it hard...
愚蠢又粗心
Stupid and careless!
您要去哪儿
Where are you going?
去找这件事的始作俑者谈谈
To talk to the man who did this.
我希望你能明白 我付出了多大代价
I hope you understand the trouble I've gone through...
才得以安排这次小小的碰头会
...to arrange this little get-together here.
很多的金钱 很多的尸体
A lot of money. A lot of dead meat.
瞧 我遇到了一个麻烦
Look, I've got a problem.
而你绝对是有本事
And you are absolutely the man...
搞定这个麻烦的人
...who possesses the gifts to take care of this problem.
我需要你杀死红头罩
I need you to murder the Red Hood.
你觉得你能搞定他吗
You think you can handle that?
我可以喝点水吗
May I have some water?
我需要一套衣服
I'm going to need something to wear...
一辆很大的卡车
...and a very big truck.
当然可以 还要什么
Sure. Anything else?
我需要几个打手
I'll need some guys.
不是这些打手 因为他们有点死了
Not these guys, because, well, they're kind of dead.
你对杰森做了什么
What did you do to Jason?
要是你装作不懂我的话
Act like you don't know what I'm talking about,
我就让你的肩膀脱节
and I'll dislocate the shoulder.
那只是开场
That's just to start.
如果你没有解除屋顶的传感器
If you haven't disabled the roof sensors,
我的护卫一分钟内就会赶到
my guards will be here in under a minute.
回答我
Answer me.
我愿意回答
I'm willing to,
但为方便起见 只要你把我口袋里的通讯器递给我
but it'll be more expedient if you hand me the communicator in my pocket...
我就命令我的人退下
...and I call off my men.
指挥官 我是雷霄·奥古
Commander, this is Ra's Al Ghul.
退下
Stand down.
我要在书房里招待一位客人
I will be entertaining a guest in my study.
你还记得我们上一次交锋吗
You remember when we last became embattled?
你策划炸毁数家银行
You were planning to blow up banks.
信达却不雅
Accurate, if inelegant.
我当时是在颠覆欧洲的经济
I was in the midst of toppling the economy of Europe,
但你偏要与我作对
but you were on to me.
我打算调开你的注意
I sought a distraction.
于是我雇佣了小丑
So I hired the Joker.
当你和他在波斯尼亚相逢时
When your paths crossed in Bosnia,
看起来像是一次不期而遇
it was to appear that you had stumbled upon him.
我付给他很大一笔钱 是想让他充当诱饵引你追错方向
He was paid extremely well for what was intended to be a wild-goose chase.
然而 他谋杀了那个孩子
Then he murdered the boy.
那不是我的主意
That was not by design.
恐怕我高估了自己控制小丑的能力
I'm afraid I overestimated my ability to control the Joker...
同时也低估了他的疯狂程度
...just as I underestimated his madness.
我为自己卷入如此残忍的事感到悲伤
It grieved me, sir, to be a party to something so brutal.
你从不避忌满手血腥
You've never shied away from drawing blood.
属实 但那些血流得有意义
True, but always with purpose.
都是为了达成伟大的目标
Always with greater goals.
而这纯属不必要的牺牲
This was simply an unnecessary casualty.
作为自我惩罚 我选择不再与你交战
As penance, I chose not to make war with you again...
并试图挽回我导致的伤害
...and to attempt to rectify this disservice.
挽回
Rectify?
是的
Yes.
我希望能将你失去的归还与你
I had hoped to return to you what you had lost.
我已在这世上行走近六个世纪
I have walked this world for nearly six centuries.
如你所知
As you know...
靠的是浸泡拉撒路坑中的回春之水
...I achieve this by bathing in the rejuvenating waters of the Lazarus Pit.
它不仅能够治病疗伤 返老还童
Along with its healing abilities,
早有传言 它还有更高的功效
it has long been rumored that it is capable of an even greater feat...
复活死者
...to raise the dead.
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
获取你的助手的遗体并不困难
Procuring the remains of your partner was not difficult.
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
美 国
大使馆
波斯尼亚  和  黑塞哥维纳  共和国
你以布鲁斯·韦恩的身份进入波斯尼亚
You had come to Bosnia under the guise of Bruce Wayne...
也以同样的身份离境
...and you chose to depart as such.
你甚至编造出一套托词
You even concocted the cover story...
说年少的杰森在萨拉热窝的一起爆炸事件中不幸罹难
...that young Jason had died in a bombing in Sarajevo.
这给我提供了便利
This made it easy for me.
只需要花一笔钱让人换出他的遗体
All it took was a few payoffs to replace his body.
我断定你不会对他进行尸检
I felt confident that you would not perform an autopsy.
即便你会 我们也争取到了足够的时间
Even if you had, we still would have bought enough time.
但我的计划
But my plan...
侦探 结果是不幸的
...well, detective, it had unfortunate results.
他回归了人世
He returned to this world...
但却心智受损
...but returned damaged.
我的军队搜寻了数月
My army searched for months,
但一直未能寻获尸体 也未发现他的踪迹
but we were never able to find a body or pick up a trail.
我以为他再一次死去了
I thought him dead yet again.
但我听说你在家乡遇到了麻烦
But I hear you have been having trouble at home.
我归还你的孩子反倒成为你家族的祸患
I have returned your son to you as a blight upon your house.
他将战火烧向你毕生守护的国度
He burns the very kingdom you protect.
我该命令警卫们追击他吗
Shall I alert the guards to pursue him?
别发傻了
Don't be foolish.
他们绝对抓不到他
They would never catch him.
再说 我不能再生事端
Besides, I have done enough.
先生 请听我劝告
Sir, please take this to heart.
杰森过去是什么样的 我们是如何失去他的
Who Jason was before, how we lost him...
以及令他复活的黑暗奇迹或说诅咒
...and this dark miracle or curse that has brought about his return,
并不是您的错
it is not your fault.
我知道您把他的死亡看作自己最沉重的失败 但是
I know you view his death as your greatest failure but...
他的生与死皆是我最沉重的失败
His life and his death are my greatest failure.
你记得当我发现他时 他是怎样的吗
Do you remember how he was when I found him?
当然 先生
Of course, sir.
无畏 自大 粗鲁 富有天资
Fearless, arrogant, brash and gifted.
哥谭警局
少 年 管 教 所
是啊 与迪克天差地别
Yes ,different then Dick in so many ways.
神奇小子
勇
但仍然蕴藏着巨大的潜力
...but still so full of potential and power.
救
市长
但我从一开始就知道 他是个危险角色
But I knew, even from the beginning, he was dangerous.
如果我没有把他训练成罗宾
lf I hadn't made him into Robin,
他将会走上邪路
he would have grown to do wrong.
后来我导致他丧命
Then I got him killed.
我的搭档
My partner.
我的士兵
My soldier.
我的过错
My fault.
我对此负责
I own that.
我牢记此事 如同我牢记一切
I'll carry that like everything else.
但现在出了这种事
But now there's this.
他运用跟我学到的一切 反过来对对付我
He's taken everything I've ever taught him and turned it on me.
这完全是我自食其果 阿尔弗雷德
It's a hell of my own making, Alfred.
先生 这不是您的错
Sir, this is not your doing.
您爱他 他心知肚明
You loved him. He knows that.
这就足够了 不够
It should be enough. It's not.
来自哥谭海湾大桥的现场报道
Reporting live from Gotham Bay Bridge...
天哪 先生 快收听媒体通讯
My word. Sir, patch into the media feed now.
快 快离开那里
Come on, get out of there, now.
我不知道那个疯子想干什么
Don't know what that maniac's up to,
但在我下达命令前 谁都不得轻举妄动
but nobody make a move till I give the order.
我是一只小茶壶 矮矮又胖胖
I'm a little teapot. Short and stout.
这是我的把手 这是我的壶嘴
Here is my handle. Here is my spout.
这不是说好的计划 你这变态
This wasn't part of the damn deal, you freak!
赶快放我出去
Get me out of here right now!
我以为你喜欢会见老面孔呢
I thought you'd enjoy seeing some old faces.
毕竟 这里的大多数人曾经是你的手下
After all, most of these guys used to work for you.
那是谁 探照灯照向他
Who's that? Get a light on him.
在那上面
Up there.
嘿 瞧瞧你 头罩男
Hey, look at you. Mr. Hood.
或者你喜欢被称作小红帽
Or do you prefer Red?
知道么 我从前也穿戴过很类似的行头
You know, I used to wear an outfit a lot like that.
我更像是衣饰奢华的餐厅领班 而不是摩托车恋物癖
Mine was more flashy maitre d' than motorcycle fetish.
你们这些后辈啊
You kids today.
对不起 你可以等等吗
I'm sorry, could you hold on?
我正忙着给你的黑帮烧把火呢
I was just in the middle of setting fire to your gang.
动手吧
Go ahead.
你以为我在乎那些人渣的死活吗
You think I care if that scum dies?
不知道 我只是想吸引你的注意
Don't know. I just wanted your attention.
我一直都在注意你
You've always had my attention.
我真正的目的就是与你会个面
But what I really wanted was an audience with you.
抱歉 这话听起来倒像是 你策划了这次海滨烧烤宴会
I'm sorry, that seems to imply that you organized this little clambake.
确实是 我当然有很多的计划
I did. Sure, I had lots of plans,
但最后阶段是把黑面具逼上绝路 迫使他达成一个协议
but the endgame was getting Black Mask so desperate that he'd cut a deal.
只有他才有关系进入阿卡姆
He was the only one with the connections to get into Arkham...
把你弄出来
...and get you out.
这年头真是谁都信不过
You can't trust anybody.
我钻进圈套里了啊
So I've been bamboozled.
惨咯
Oh, my.
我不会夸口把你手到擒来
I wouldn't undersell it.
为了我们的重聚 可费了我不少工夫
It took a lot of work to bring about our reunion.
重聚 我们以前见过吗
Reunion? Have we met before?
是的 见过
Yes, we have.
为了把记忆蒸发出来
Well, here's to warm memories.
我抓到他了
I've got him.
你想要他吗 在犯罪巷见我
You want him? Meet me at crime alley.
好吧
Okay.
那么 有什么计划
So, what's the plan?
睡眠聚会 字谜游戏
Slumber party? Charades?
真心话大冒险
A little Truth or Dare?
好 我先冒一把险
Yes. I'll start with "dare."
哦 也许我该选择说真话
Well, maybe I'll just go with "truth."
告诉我 滋味好受吗
Tell me, how does that feel?
知道么 仅当我笑的时候才会痛
You know, it only hurts when I laugh.
不过 嘿 我得知道
But, hey, I gotta know.
你是谁
Who are you?
你说我们认识彼此
You said we knew one another,
你也确实看着眼熟
and you do seem really familiar.
我们在校园舞会上是一对儿
We double at the prom?
又或者我们一起炸过校车
Or maybe blow up a school bus together?
不 是你造就了今日的我
No. I'm just something you helped make.
说得很隐晦
That's pretty cryptic...
但够有趣
...but interesting.
多说点
Tell me more.
没问题 听好了
Sure. Listen up.
不是真的吧
Unreal.
你好
Hello.
很高兴你能来
So glad you could make it.
今晚了断一切恩怨
This ends tonight. All of it.
对此我比任何人都更清楚
Nobody knows that better than me.
哈 你有不少玩意儿
Ha. Oh, you and your gadgets.
你不是唯一有玩具的人
You're not the only one with toys.
糟糕
Crap.
看看你
Look at you.
为了公平起见
I guess we should keep it even.
杰森
Jason.
是我
Yes.
我不想和你打
I don't wanna fight you.
你的行为与言辞完全相反
All evidence to the contrary.
拜托 让我帮助你
Please, I can help you.
我知道发生了什么事
I know what happened.
哦 你找雷霄谈过了吧
Oh, you got to talking with Ra's, huh?
这么想会不会让你如释重负
Does it make it easier for you to think that...
是他的回春泉把我扭曲成了一个狂魔
...my little dip in his fountain of youth turned me rabid?
又或者这才是真正的我
Or is this just the real me?
告诉我
Tell me...
哪件事更令你不安
...what bothers you more,
你最沉重的失败从坟墓中归来
that your greatest failure has returned from the grave?
还是我成为比你更出色的蝙蝠侠
Or that I've become a better Batman than you?
你通过胁迫和谋杀来统治黑道
You're ruling through intimidation and murder.
你不过是另一个罪犯
You're just another criminal.
我才是这座城市所需要的
I'm what this city needs.
全身上下都藏有装备
Hidden goodies all over, huh?
咱俩都是活的军火库
We're both just a couple of walking armories.
也许吧 但我们来看看 你没了玩具还能玩出什么来
Maybe so, but let's see how you do without your toys.
够了 结束了
Enough. it's over.
你说你想超越我
You say you wanna be better than me.
但这是不可能的
But it won't happen.
你走错路了
Not like this.
我知道我对不起你
I know I failed you,
但我尽力去救你了 杰森
but I tried to save you, Jason.
我我现在也在尽力救你
I'm... I'm trying to save you now.
你以为我是为了这个原因吗
Is that what you think this is about?
因为你没能救我一命
That you let me die?
我不知道什么更能遮蔽你的判断力
I don't know what clouds your judgment worse.
你的内疚 还是迂腐的道德感
Your guilt or your antiquated sense of morality.
布鲁斯 我原谅你你没能救我
Bruce, I forgive you for not saving me.
但为什么 到底是为什么
But why? Why on God's earth...
他还活着
...is he still alive?
这孩子说到点子上啦
Gotta give the boy points.
他千辛万苦从冥界爬回人间 来举办这场狂欢舞会
He came all the way back from the dead to make this shindig happen.
谁带了照相机
So who's got a camera?
哦哦 先给我和这孩子合张影
Ooh! Ooh! Get one of me and the kid first.
然后是咱俩 然后是咱们仨
Then you and me, then the three of us.
再然后拍一张拿着撬棍的 然后
And then one with the crowbar. Then...
闭上你的臭嘴 否则我先朝你的大腿开一枪
You'll be as quiet as possible or I'll put one in your lap first.
扫兴鬼 不给你蛋糕吃
Party pooper. No cake for you.
你忽视他迄今犯下的一切恶行
Ignoring what he's done in the past.
盲目、愚蠢地漠视他所填满的大片墓地
Blindly, stupidly, disregarding the entire graveyards he's filled,
成百上千的受害者 无数的生离死别
the thousands who have suffered, the friends he's crippled.
你知道么 我还以为
You know, I thought...
我还以为 我的死 会让你不再任由他害人
I thought I'd be the last person you'd ever let him hurt.
如果当初被他打得血肉模糊的是你
If it had been you that he beat to a bloody pulp,
如果他杀死的是你
if he had taken you from this world,
我只会做一件事情…
I would've done nothing...
就是掘地三尺也要挖出 这个恶贯满盈的刽子手
...but search the planet for this pathetic pile of evil death-worshipping garbage...
并送他下地狱
...and sent him off to hell.
你不明白
You don't understand.
我认为你从来都不明白
I don't think you've ever understood.
什么
What?
你的道德守则不允许那么做
What, your moral code just won't allow for that?
越过那条线太困难了
It's too hard to cross that line?
不 天哪 不是的
No! God Almighty, no.
那真是再容易不过了
It'd be too damned easy.
我唯一想做的就是杀死他
All I've ever wanted to do is kill him.
没有哪一天我不想着
A day doesn't go by I don't think about subjecting him...
把他对别人的一切折磨 全都施加到他自己身上
...to every horrendous torture he's dealt out to others...
然后结果他的狗命
...and then end him.
啊 原来你确实对我朝思暮想
Aw. So you do think about me.
但如果我那么做了
But if I do that,
如果我允许自己走上杀戮之路
if I allow myself to go down into that place,
我将永远无法回头
I'll never come back.
为什么
Why?
我不是说要杀企鹅 稻草人 或者丹特
I'm not talking about killing Penguin or Scarecrow or Dent.
我说的是杀他 只杀他一个
I'm talking about him. Just him.
杀他是因为
And doing it because...
因为他害得你我天人永隔
Because he took me away from you.
我办不到 对不起
I can't. I'm sorry.
真甜蜜
That is so sweet.
但是 你别无选择
Well, you won't have a choice.
我不会 我做的都是为了这一刻
I won't-This is what it's all been about.
这一刻
This.
你 我 他
You, and me and him.
到你作出决定的时候了
Now is the time you decide.
如果你不愿意杀这个肮脏的精神病 我来杀
If you won't kill this psychotic piece of filth, I will.
如果你要阻止我 就必须杀了我
If you wanna stop me, you're gonna have to kill me.
你知道我不会
You know I won't...
我会打爆他病态的大脑
I'm gonna blow his deranged brains out.
如果你要阻止这件事 就必须对我开枪
And if you wanna stop it, you are gonna have to shoot me.
对着我的脸开枪
Right in my face!
故事的发展比我预期的更精彩
This is turning out even better than I'd hoped.
他还是我 你自己决定
It's him or me, you have to decide!
现在就决定 快
Decide now. Do it!
他还是我 决定啊
Him or me? Decide!
不敢相信你打中他了
I can't believe you got him.
你不愧是眼疾手快 百发百中的哥谭神射手
You expert, rooting-tooting, eagle-eyed, goth-loving marksman.
我爱死你了
I love it.
你打出了神之一手
You managed to find a way to win.
而且每个人还是都输了
And everybody still loses.
不 别搅局 这样更好
No, don't spoil it. This is better.
我是今晚唯一得偿所愿的人
I'm the only one who's gonna get what he wants tonight.
哦耶 大…爆…炸
Yes, bing, bang, boom.
咱们都死在一块儿了
We all go out together.
你不喜欢圆满大结局吗
Don't you just love a happy ending?
与地区检察官办公室 关系密切的知情人士
Sources close to the district attorney's office...
暗示说这起案件很有可能 会因证据不足而不予起诉
...have intimated the case will most likely be dropped due to lack of evidence.
但黑面具仍然受到调查 因为他涉嫌
But the Black Mask is still under investigation for his alleged complicity...
协助小丑逃离阿卡姆
...in Joker's escape from Arkham.
两名因协助小丑越狱而受到指控的警卫
The two guards charged with aiding and abetting the escape...
今天下午在哥谭法院的牢房中被人杀死
...were found murdered this afternoon in the Gotham courthouse jail,
黑
面
具
怀疑是犯罪集团头目黑面具所为
while the alleged crime lord known as Black Mask...
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
但他在交纳一百万美元保释金后获释
...was released on $1 million bail for his suspected involvement...
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
黑
面
具
并等待日后的听证会
...and is currently awaiting a hearing.
同时 小丑被押回了阿卡姆精神病院
Meanwhile, the Joker has been returned to Arkham Asylum.
负责官员宣称 已采取特别措施
Officials there claim that extra measures have been taken...
确保他不可能再次越狱
...to ensure another escape would be impossible.
黑面具在被捕之前 受到了神秘的红头罩的暴力攻击
Prior to his arrest, Black Mask was being strong-armed by the mysterious Red Hood.
先生
Sir,
考虑到最近发生的事 您想让我把它移走吗
in light of all the recent events, would you like me to remove that?
不
No.
这并不改变任何事
This doesn't change anything.
一丝一毫都没有改变
It doesn't change anything at all.
好了 我们走
Okay, let's go.
如果你在家都不能快速着装
If you can't suit up quickly at home base,
我很担心你执行任务的效率
I'm concerned how you would handle it in the field.
也许他正对着镜子梳妆打扮呢
Perhaps he's primping.
我还记得 理查德少爷第一次披上披风时
As I recall, Master Richard spent nearly half an hour admiring his reflection...
花了大约半个小时孤芳自赏
...the first time he donned his cape.
杰森 赶快过来 否则我就独自巡逻去了
Jason, get on out here or I'm going on patrol without you.
哈 天哪
Ha! My word.
吃惊吧 差一点
Gotcha. Would have...
因为三分钟前我就看见你 偷偷溜到了计算机阵列的后面
...if I hadn't seen you slip behind the computer banks three minutes ago.
-不 我吓到你啦 -感觉怎么样
No, I got you. How does it feel?
感觉酷毙了
It feels awesome.
看我的吧 我是罗宾 神奇小子
Check me out. I'm Robin, the Boy Wonder.
开玩笑吧 这太棒了
Are you kidding me? This rocks.
快走吧 老头 有坏人等着我们去抓
Come on, old man, we've got bad guys who need chasing.
这是我一生中最幸福的一天
This is the best day of my life.